(
"ai_sub_version": "3.3.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-24T00:08:08.411239",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ときのおそら お披露目誕生日2026
[Tokino Sora Birthday Party 2026]
高鳴る心臓に祈りを乗せて
Placing a prayer upon my throbbing heart,
曖昧な夢を描く
I draw an ambiguous dream.
幻想は想像のまま
If fantasy remains just an imagination,
終われないんだ
it cannot end like this.
みんな、今日見に来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you so much for coming to watch today!
答えを延々と探し続けて
Endlessly searching for the answer,
何者かになりたくて
wanting to become someone,
潸々と降る夕立をただ眺めた
I merely stared at the pouring evening shower.
優しく寄り添って心が晴れるのなら
If gently being by your side clears up my heart,
翼が生えたような気がして
I feel as though wings have grown on me,
いつだって隣にいるから
because I'll always be by your side.
だって言葉紡いで唄うことがわたしの運命だ
Because spinning words and singing is my destiny.
世界にありふれた虚しささえも上書きして
Overwriting even the emptiness common in this world,
路地裏に咲いた花のように願いを照らす
it illuminates my wishes like a flower blooming in a back alley,
小さな光に憧れて
longing for a small light.
名前を持たない歌なんて
A song without a name...
神様は認めてくれない
...won't be acknowledged by God.
一つ一つ枯れない花のように
Each one like a flower that never withers,
昨日の自分にさよならして零れた涙
saying goodbye to yesterday's self, and the tears that fell...
うまく笑えなくてもいいかな保存
Is it okay if I can't smile well?
だって理想は遠ざかってくばかり
Because my ideals only keep drifting away,
もう散々だよ
I'm so sick of it.
どれだけ手を伸ばして叫んだって届かないの
No matter how much I reach out and scream, it doesn't reach.
望めばいつか叶うはずって信じてる
Believing that if I wish, it will come true someday.
どうか歌よ響いて
Please, let my song resonate!
あぁ心臓の鼓動が今日もうるさい
Ah, the beating of my heart is loud today too...
行き止まりばっか足が竦んで立てないよ
I'm always hitting dead ends, my legs freeze and I can't stand.
音のない世界から君を見つけて連れ出すんだ
I'll find you in this soundless world and lead you out.
言葉紡いで唄うことがわたしの運命だ
Weaving words together to sing is my destiny.
世界にありふれた虚しささえも上書きして
Overwriting even the emptiness so common in this world.
路地裏に咲いた花のように願いを照らす
Shining a light on wishes, like a flower blooming in a back alley.
小さな光に憧れて
Yearning for a small light.
君の歌姫になれたらいいな
I hope I can become your diva...
いいな
...I hope so.
Okey dokey 返事はいいけど
Okey-dokey, your reply is fine, but...
冗談なら笑えないよ
...if it's a joke, it's not funny.
渋滞 曖昧 どっちを向いちゃうの
Congestion, ambiguity, which way are we facing?
蜃気楼に手を伸ばした
I reached my hand out to a mirage.
微熱のような夢物語
A dreamlike story like a slight fever.
そんな光は見ない振りしてた
I pretended not to see that light.
ざわめく鼓動 まだ行かないで
My buzzing heartbeat, please don't go yet.
幻じゃ嫌だよ 私を奪って
I don't want it to be an illusion, take me away.
魅惑 of 斬新ダンスインマインド
A captivating, innovative dance in mind.
広がって収まんないユニバース
An expanding, uncontrollable universe.
君の表情は私の森羅万象を
Your expression completely changes my universe,
書き換えちゃうかも 責任重大ね
you might rewrite it all, so it's a big responsibility.
一切合切
Absolutely everything.
dance dance dance we are dancing reed
夢中になって絡み合ったゼログラビティ
Becoming captivated and intertwined in zero gravity.
構わず dance dance dance
Without a care, dance, dance, dance.
just a dance just a dance
声は闇に預けたまま
Leaving our voices in the darkness.
目を覚ましても離れないで
Even when I wake up, don't leave me.
Maybe needy 正気じゃないのよ
Maybe needy, I'm not in my right mind.
体温が忘れられない
I can't forget your body heat.
誰彼そんなんじゃないから
Because it's not just about anyone.
独り占めして euphoria
Monopolizing this euphoria.
気にしてない様な言葉は装飾で
Words that seem casual are just decorations,
メイクの様には流せない
they can't be washed away like makeup.
360° 偽りだって
Even if it's 360 degrees of lies,
隠しきれぬような 私に構って
I can't seem to hide it, pay attention to me.
嬉しいなんて crazy crazy love
Calling it joy, a crazy, crazy love.
摩天楼から連れ去って
Take me away from the skyscraper.
君の表情は私の深層心理を
Your expression replaces my deep psychology,
すり替えちゃうのよ 責任重大ね
it's a heavy responsibility.
過ぎ去ったネオン残像 shooting star
The passing neon afterimage, a shooting star.
グライダーみたいに漂えば
If I drift like a glider,
幸も不幸もなかった保存
there was neither happiness nor unhappiness.
指先でまた君を探している保存
I'm searching for you again with my fingertips.
その声を聴かせてよ 私に構って
Let me hear that voice, pay attention to me.
教えてよ 恋の先を！
Tell me what lies beyond love!
広がって収まんないユニバース
An expanding, uncontrollable universe.
君の存在は私の将来までも
Your existence steps into even my future,
踏み込んだのよ 付き合ってよね
so stay with me.
一切合切
Absolutely everything.
dance dance dance we are dancing reed
夢中になって絡み合ったゼログラビティ
Intertwined and engrossed in zero gravity.
構わず dance dance dance
Without a care, dance, dance, dance.
just a dance just a dance
声は闇に預けたまま
Leaving our voices in the darkness.
目を覚ましても離れないで
Even when I wake up, don't leave me.
みんなー！今日は誕生日ライブに来てくれてありがとうー！
Everyone! Thank you so much for coming to my birthday live stream today!
イェーイ！
Yay!
コメントも見えてるよー！
I can see your comments too!
最初に聴いてもらったのが、『Diva』『Dancing Reed』でした！
The first two songs you heard were 'Diva' and 'Dancing Reed'!
えー、この二つの曲は、あの、フェスと、あと去年のね、ドラマの主題歌に
These two songs were used for the festival and as theme songs for last year's drama.
使わせて、使っていただいた曲で、すごく思い出に残っているので
They are very memorable to me,
最初に二曲歌ってみようかなと思って選びました！
so I chose them to perform first!
そして！今回はですね
And! This time,
ときのそらお披露目誕生日
it's the Tokino Sora Reveal Birthday...
2026… ときのそらおじゃないよ。ときのそらだよ！
...2026! It's not 'Tokino Sorao', it's 'Tokino Sora'!
みんなのつぶやきを待っているので
Yes, I'm waiting for everyone's tweets,
たくさんつぶやいてほしいな。トレンドに入るかな？
so please tweet a lot! I wonder if we'll trend?
ねえ。
Right?
そして、今回のテーマは
And the theme this time,
ハッシュを象徴する無限をモチーフに
with "infinity" symbolizing the hash (#) as a motif,
宇宙や星をステージに散りばめて
has space and stars scattered on the stage,
中毒性のあるビート、リズムの曲で絡めた
mixed with songs of addictive beats and rhythms,
えー、デジタルパルスライブです！
it's a Digital Pulse Live!
デジタルパルスライブです！
A Digital Pulse Live!
こちらね、大きな天球が曲によってどう変わるのかを
Please watch how this large celestial sphere
見ていてください。
changes depending on the song.
そしてね、今年ののんのんは、えー、5つなので
And this year, there are five Non-nons,
くるくる回転してます。くるくるくるくる。
and they are spinning around. Spin, spin, spin!
そして、夜空にはソラザウルスもいるよ。
And there's also Sorasaurus in the night sky.
ソラザウルスはね、なんとね
Sorasaurus can now actually
炎を吐けるようになりました。
breathe fire!
ぷふー。
Pffft.
あん肝もね、ちゃんとあん肝さまもあるんですけど
We also have Ankimo, Ankimo-sama is here too,
見えるかな？
can you see him?
もちろん、あと今年も新衣装のお披露目や
Of course, please also look forward to
告知したゲストと、えー、あと
the new outfit reveal, the announced guests,
どんな曲を披露するのかも楽しみにしていてくださいね。
and what songs we will perform!
そして、次に行く前に
And before we move on,
プチお披露目、最初にしちゃいましょう！
let's do a mini-reveal first!
カメラさん、上を向いてください。
Mr. Camera, please look up.
はい！というわけでね
Okay! And so,
新しいクワガタヘア、新髪型お披露目です！
this is my new stag beetle hair! A new hairstyle reveal!
それでは早速ゲストパート行ってみよう。
Now let's head straight into the guest part.
可愛い、ありがとう。おお、可愛い、ありがとう！
"Cute," thank you! Oh, "cute," thank you!
シロ組さんもいっぱいコメントしててね。
Siro-gumi members, please leave lots of comments too!
最初のゲストは、この人です！
The first guest is this person!
電脳少女シロ
[Guest: Cyber Girl Siro]
星の降るたびに
Every time stars fall,
恋をするたびに
Every time we fall in love,
バイバイ だって、夜はギャラクティカ
Bye-bye, because the night is galactica.
明星ギャラクティカ
[Song: Myoujou Galactica]
今夜は宇宙のアイオライトが
Tonight, the cosmic iolite is...
いやに眩しいから
...far too dazzling.
街のネオン
The city neon...
星の宿り
...and the starry shelter...
逃げようか ふたり
...shall we escape there, the two of us?
シドけナイくらい揺らぐグラスが
The glass wobbling so helplessly...
ココロ惑わすから
...bewitches my heart.
あなただけ
Only you...
今夜だけ
...only tonight...
星ハシゴかける
...we build a ladder to the stars.
見つめ あなたの表情
Staring at your expression,
照らして 明星ギャラクティカ
shine upon us, Myoujou Galactica.
見上げた
Looking up...
瞳が
...your eyes, the universe...
キラキラって光る
...are sparkling bright.
近づくほどにHold on
As we draw closer, hold on,
ねえ孤独ごと抱きしめて
embrace even my loneliness.
ふたりの
In our...
手と手が
...hands, like stars...
交じりあって 恋はギャラクティカ
...intertwine, love is galactica.
パッパッパッパヤ パッパッパッパヤ
Pa-pa-pa-paya, pa-pa-pa-paya,
pa-pa-pa-paya, pa-pa-pa-paya.
嗚呼 同じペースで
Ah, at the same pace,
泳ぎだすペイブメント
we start to swim along the pavement.
宵と宵で繋ぐ朝へ
Connecting night to night towards the morning,
一度きりのダンス
with this once-in-a-lifetime dance.
あなたとわたしの 灯す星の行方は
The direction of the star that you and I light up,
何光年先を指した？
how many light-years away does it point?
結ぶオリオンの愛の星が
Because the loving stars of Orion we connect...
真っ赤に燃えるから
...are burning crimson.
今夜だけ
Only tonight...
あまのじゃくだから
...because we are contrarians.
見つめ あなたの表情
Staring at your expression,
隠して 明星ギャラクティカ
hide it, Myoujou Galactica.
そのトキめいた気持ちが道だって
Even if those fluttering feelings are the path,
手探りでいいから
it's fine to just grope our way.
生まれたままの衝動
Our raw, newborn impulses,
パッパッパヤ パッパパパヤ
Pa-pa-pa-ya, pa-pa-pa-pa-ya
はい！というわけで、最初のゲストはシロちゃんだよ！
All right! So, our very first guest is... Shiro-chan!
こんにちは！ときの、シロです！
Hello! This is Tokino... Shiro!
あ、ときのシロになっちゃった！
Ah, she became Tokino Shiro!
本当に今日はそらちゃん、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Sora-chan, happy birthday to you! Congratulations!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
すごいね、格好！
That's an amazing outfit!
そらちゃんという歌姫に会えると聞いて、出せるものは全部出して行こうと思います。
Hearing I'd meet a diva like Sora-chan, I thought I should show off everything I've got.
そ、そういうことだったんだ。待って、これチャンネルBANしちゃったら…
Oh, so that was the reason. Wait, if this gets the channel banned...
そんなことない！
No way!
ごめんなさい！大丈夫、大丈夫。胸が苦しくなってきました！大丈夫。
I'm sorry! I'm fine, I'm fine. Oh, my chest is tightening! I'm okay.
あ、そらちゃん、クラゲさんには注射器があると聞きます。
Sora-chan, I heard jellyfish have stingers.
注射器？
Stingers?
毒針をぜひ、頭でごちゅんと後ろに刺していただけませんか？
Could you please bonk me on the head with your stinger?
ごちゅん！
Bonk!
うっ、ううっ、倒れる、倒れちゃう…
Ugh... I'm collapsing, I'm going to collapse...
すごい効いてきました！
It's working so well!
効いてきた？
It's working?
皆さん、そらちゃんは変わりました。毒針を持った女に変わったんです！
Everyone, Sora-chan has changed. She turned into a woman with a deadly stinger!
そう、私強くなったから！
That's right, because I've gotten stronger!
そらちゃんは毒針が持ちたくて、可愛いクラゲヘアになったんですか？
Did you get this cute jellyfish hair just to have a stinger, Sora-chan?
違う違う。私はやっぱり、アイドルと言えばこういう可愛い髪型の人が多いかなと思って、そういうアイドルっぽい髪型にしたいなと思ってたんだよね。
No, no! I just thought idols usually have cute hairstyles like this, so I wanted to try a more idol-like look.
はぁ〜。そらちゃん聞いてください。私もアイドルしかないし、歌姫でしかないのに、ディーバっていう曲もあるんですけど、今もアイドルであろうとこう…なんか、なってるのに…
Sigh... Sora-chan, listen to me. I'm also nothing but an idol and a diva, and I even have a song called "Diva," but even as I try to be an idol...
なんか、なってるのに…
Even though I'm trying so hard...
努力してくれる姿がもう大好きで、食べたいくらい。
But I love how hard you work so much, I want to eat you up!
食べちゃうの？
You're going to eat me?
シナモンロールみたいですね。見てカメラさん、見て見て！
You look like a cinnamon roll. Look, Camera-san, look!
これはシナモンロール？
Is this a cinnamon roll?
シナモンロール。食べられてる、食べられてる。
Cinnamon roll! I'm eating you, I'm eating you up.
うふふ、ありがとう。
Ehehe, thank you.
はい、ということで。
And so...
今日はBANされない発言を心がけていきます！
Today, I will do my best to make family-friendly comments that won't get us banned!
もうすでに結構シロちゃんワールド炸裂してますけど。
You've already let the "Shiro-chan World" explode quite a bit, though.
あの、なんかこんな、大好きなそらちゃんのこんな場に、そらともさんたちと一緒に祝ってもらえると思わなくて。ありがとう。
Well, I just didn't expect to be able to celebrate with Soratomos at my beloved Sora-chan's special event. Thank you.
3年ぶりだよ。
It's been three years.
あ！3年ぶりの元カノです。
Ah! I'm your ex-girlfriend of three years.
元カノじゃない、そらともさん！
Not your ex-girlfriend! You mean Soratomos!
そらともさん、一緒に、一緒に、独り占めしないので、愛でていきましょう。
Soratomos, let's love her together. I won't keep her all to myself.
今日はそらともさんに、シロの来た意味を分からせたいと思います。そらちゃん立ってください。
Today, I want to show all the Soratomos why Shiro came here today. Sora-chan, please stand up.
はい。
Okay.
3, 2, 1
Three, two, one...
バニーガールズ！
Bunny Girls!
このスクショでいいの？ねぇ。
Is this a good screenshot pose? Hey.
千手観音、千手観音。
Thousand-Armed Kannon! Thousand-Armed Kannon!
千手観音？
Thousand-Armed Kannon?
そらちゃん、新衣装のバニー衣装プレゼントしに来ました！
Sora-chan, I came to present you with your new bunny outfit!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
どうですか？
What do you think?
可愛い、うさ耳も可愛い！
It's so cute! The bunny ears are adorable too!
うさぎさんって万年発情してるので、ちょっとハァハァしてもらって…
Bunnies are in heat all year round, so could you pant a little bit...
え？
What?
可愛いー！
So cute!
私のしっぽもあるよ。
Look, I have a tail too.
あ！そうだ、そらちゃんといえば、しっぽは？
Ah! That's right, speaking of Sora-chan, what about your tail?
そう、ちょっと…
Yeah, it's right...
ちょっと触ってもいいですか？
Can I touch it for a second?
いいよ。
Sure.
ツンツン、あっ、あっ、大変！
Poke, poke... Oh, oh no!
何？
What is it?
シロ、発情が止まらないので、そろそろおうちに帰ります！
Shiro's heat won't stop, so it's time for me to go home!
帰っちゃうの？
You're going home?!
はい！月からみんなを見守っています。この後も楽しんでね！
Yes! I'll be watching over everyone from the moon. Enjoy the rest of the stream!
楽しんでね、ありがとう！
Have fun! Thank you!
あ、なんか出てきてる。
Oh, something's coming out.
ちょっと、帰れてないよ！
Wait, you haven't fully left yet!
シロちゃんワールド炸裂で、楽しかったね。なんだこれって言わないでね、みんな。ねー。
That was a full-on explosion of the Shiro-chan World. Please don't ask "What was that?" everyone, okay?
でも、相変わらずのシロちゃんで、私一緒に歌えてとっても楽しかったです。マイペースだね、ねー、マイペースだよ。
But she's still the same old Shiro-chan. I had so much fun singing with her! She really goes at her own pace.
私もマイペースだから、良いコンビってことだ。
I go at my own pace too, so that makes us a great duo!
というわけで、続いてのゲストに行きましょう！この人です！
So, let's move on to the next guest! Here they are!
全部全部あんたのせいだ 反吐が出るぐらいにウザったいわ
It's all, all your fault. It's so annoying I want to throw up.
何かに縋って諂って 期待した私がバカだった
Clinging to something, flattering... I was a fool to expect anything.
ご機嫌伺いの八方美人 それ家でアンチ内職に一生懸命
Pleasing everyone as a yes-man, while diligently working as an online troll at home.
浅いキャパシティ 毎度おきに 詰まるとこ人生ずっと地味
Shallow capacity, thanks every time. In short, your life is always plain.
見苦しい 痛い 正しい 無視できないのがいっそ腹立たしい
Unsightly, painful, "correct". It's rather annoying that I can't ignore it.
苛立たしい そろそろ飽きた自画自賛に
Irritating. I'm getting tired of your self-praise.
Likeの反対はApathy 歪なイコールで繋がれた証
The opposite of "like" is apathy. Proof that we are connected by a distorted equal sign.
切り離せない関係 そらしてしまいたいわ
A relationship that can't be severed. I want to turn my eyes away.
これは言わゆるヘイトスピーチ
This is what you call hate speech.
匿名性の生命を声明に乗せてんだ
Putting anonymous life into a declaration.
鳴り止まないサイレン 掻き消すために痙攣
The siren that won't stop ringing, convulsing to drown it out.
悪魔になりきってチュってする
Playing the demon and blowing a kiss.
大嫌い あんたのこと私 大大嫌い
I hate you. I really, really hate you.
重い 絡み避けたい もはや バイバイバイバイしたい
Heavy, I want to avoid the entanglement, I already want to say bye-bye-bye-bye.
脳内 妄想の海に 溺れ 溺れ 溺れたい
Inside my brain, I want to drown, drown, drown in the sea of delusion.
どうだい？ 私のこと あんた 大大大嫌いになった？
How about it? Did you come to really, really, really hate me?
嗚呼 100倍返し散らし死なし死なし もし隣り合わ並べても 2コティン無し
Ah, returning it a hundredfold, scattering, dying... even if we are placed side-by-side, no nicotine.
I miss youって近づいた結末は 凡ミス 凡ミス センキュー 犯名教室
The ending of getting closer saying "I miss you" is a simple mistake, simple mistake. Thank you, classroom of the culprit's name.
あとは自意識一生消えてくんないわ
After that, my self-consciousness won't disappear for the rest of my life.
よしよし良い子ね 愛嬌振り撒きパラパラ良い子ね
There, there, good girl. Scattering charm around, a scatterbrained good girl.
だけどだけどその本性は 善悪の区別もつかないの？
But, but is her true nature unable to distinguish between good and evil?
減点方式 取り巻く環境に丸め込まれて
Deduction system, getting sweet-talked by the surrounding environment...
生涯大体巻き込まれたって 当然の報いに変わっちゃった
...even if I get dragged into it for life, it turned into a natural retribution.
表は鏡なんです つまるところ依存は両辺で
The surface is a mirror. In short, the dependence is on both sides.
遮断しても付き纏う 己の弱さが腑甲斐無い
Even if blocked, it clings. My own weakness is pathetic.
全部全部あんたのせいって 反吐が出るくらいに止まんないわ
Saying "it's all, all your fault" - it doesn't stop to the point of throwing up.
いっそのこと切り離せたら 軽くなれるのにな
If only we could sever ties, we could have become so much lighter.
大嫌い あんたのこと私 大大嫌い
I hate you. I really, really hate you.
重い 絡み避けたい もはや バイバイバイバイしたい
Heavy, I want to avoid the entanglement, I already want to say bye-bye-bye-bye.
脳内 妄想の海に 溺れ 溺れ 溺れたい
Inside my brain, I want to drown, drown, drown in the sea of delusion.
どうだい？ 私のこと あんた 大大大嫌いになった？
How about it? Did you come to really, really, really hate me?
嗚呼 100倍返し散らし死なし死なし もし隣り合わ並べても 2コティン無し
Ah, returning it a hundredfold, scattering, dying... even if we are placed side-by-side, no nicotine.
I miss youって近づいた結末は 凡ミス 凡ミス センキュー 犯名教室
The ending of getting closer saying "I miss you" is a simple mistake, simple mistake. Thank you, classroom of the culprit's name.
あとは自意識一生消えてくんないわ
After that, my self-consciousness won't disappear for the rest of my life.
イェーイ！ イェーイ！
Yay! Yay!
どうも！
Thank you!
はい、というわけでゲストは、ゆいちゃんです！
Yes! So, our guest is... Yui-chan!
はーい！改めまして、Neo-Porte所属の緋月ゆいです！そらさん、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Yes! Once again, I'm Hizuki Yui, belonging to Neo-Porte! Sora-san, happy birthday!
ありがとう！来てくれて嬉しい！ - おめでとう！
Thank you! I'm so glad you came! - Congratulations!
1年ぶり！ - 1年ぶり！
It's been a year! - It's been a year!
ねー、去年はね、ちょっと残念ながらメッセージだけで... - あの、本当に...
Yes, last year was unfortunately just a video message... - Um, really...
申し訳ございませんでした！ - いや、メッセージでもね、すごくみんな「おおー！」ってなってて
I am terribly sorry! - No, even with the message, everyone was like, "Whoa!"
嬉しかったですよ！ - すごいガラガラ声で、去年は...
I was so happy! - My voice was so raspy last year...
参加させていただいたんですけど、今年はリベンジができてとっても嬉しいです！
...when I participated, but I'm so happy I could have my revenge this year!
やった！リベンジだ！ - 呼んでいただいて嬉しいです。ありがとうございます！
Yay! Revenge! - I'm so happy you invited me. Thank you very much!
こちらこそ！今回の曲もね、私が選んだんですけども
Likewise! I chose this song for us this time...
やっぱりあの、ゆいちゃんといえば、かっこいい声っていうのがすごく私の中で
...because when I think of Yui-chan, I think of your cool voice, and that was really in my head.
あ、かっこいいよ！ - へえ、嬉しいです。かっこいいよ、って。
Oh, you're cool! - Oh, I'm glad. "You're cool."
なので、このデュエットっていうのもあるので、この曲をぜひ一緒に歌いたいと思って
So since it's a duet, I really wanted to sing this song together...
嬉しい！ - リクエストしました！ - ありがとうございます！ - どうだったかな？
I'm so happy! - ...so I requested it! - Thank you! - How was it?
いや、あの、歌も超難しかったんですけど、
Well, the singing was super difficult, too...
どっちかっていうとダンスが、普段あんまりしないので - そうだよね
...but more than that, I don't usually dance much, so... - Right.
ちょっとそらさんとダンスレッスンなどもね、やらせていただきましてですね
I got to practice dance lessons with Sora-san...
あ、したの！したの！ - 本番に向けて準備してまいりました！
Ah, we did! We did! - ...and we prepared for the actual performance!
ねー、でも振りはめちゃくちゃ速くてびっくりした！ - いやいや、恐縮でございます
Yes, but the choreography was incredibly fast, I was shocked! - No, no, I am humbled. Nus.
ちょっとね、「あー」って言いながらダンスして（笑） - そうそうそう（笑）
We were like, "Ah!" while dancing. - Exactly (laughs).
間奏でターンするところがあったんですけど、みなさん。
There was a part in the instrumental break where we turned, everyone.
ターンが本当に体幹がなさすぎて、「あー！」って何回もよろけてですね、大変だったんですけど...
I have so little core strength that during the turns, I kept stumbling and going "Ah!", so it was really tough...
いや、でも本番は完璧だったんじゃないの？ - あ、良かったです！
But didn't you do it perfectly during the actual performance? - Oh, thank goodness!
いや、素晴らしい！ - 良かった、よろけなくて。めっちゃ頭の中で「よろけんじゃね、よろけんじゃね」と思いながら（笑）
No, you were amazing! - I'm glad I didn't stumble. In my head, I kept thinking, "Don't stumble, don't stumble!" (laughs)
そうだよね - 「よろけないように」っていうことを考えながら。
Right. - While constantly thinking, "Keep steady."
意識しちゃうよね - 意識してました。そらさんが完璧なんで、ダンス。
You end up focusing on it, right? - I was focusing on it. Sora-san is perfect at dancing, after all.
いやいや、そんなことないから！ - だから、隣に立つから、私もよろけないようにしないとって思って
No, no, not at all! - So since I stood next to you, I felt I had to make sure I wouldn't stumble either.
上手くいって良かったです！ - いや、本当に私も...
I'm so glad it went well! - Yes, honestly, I also...
まさかね、ダンスまでしてくれるとは思わなかったの。だから本当に、
I never expected you to dance with me! So really...
誘った時に「ダンスもあるんですけど...」って言った時に、
when I invited you and said, "There is also dancing..."
「え、ダンス？ちょっと...」ってなるかなって思ったから、
I thought you might say, "Oh, dancing? Well..."
「是非！」って思いまして、本当に。
But I thought, "I'd love to!", really.
普段ね、こう、右手でどうにかしてるんで、
Usually, you know, I manage somehow with my right hand...
手持ちマイクで右手でどうにか尺稼ぎしてたんですけど、
using a handheld mic to kill time with my right hand, but today...
今日はダンスに挑戦できたのが、すごく自分的にも嬉しかったです。一緒に。
being able to challenge dancing made me really happy. Together.
めちゃくちゃカッコよかった！
You were incredibly cool!
いやいや、一緒に踊れて超嬉しかったんで。ありがとうございます！
No, no, I was super happy to dance with you. Thank you so much!
どうでしたか？
How was it?
どうだった？
How was it, everyone?
カッコよかったでしょ？ 頑張ったぞ！ 頑張ったよ！
Incredibly cool, right? We worked hard! We did our best!
はい。
Yes.
という感じで、この後もね、またライブがあるということなので、
And like this, since we have more of the live show coming up...
この後もぜひ、頑張ってください！
please do your best for the rest of the show too!
頑張る！ 応援してます！ ありがとう！
I will! I'm cheering for you! Thank you!
はい、ということで、AZKiでした！ありがとうございました！
Alright, and that was AZKi! Thank you so much!
ありがとうございました！ 頑張ってね！
Thank you so much! Good luck!
ありがとうね！ バイバーイ！
Thank you! Bye-bye!
というわけで、ひづきちゃんが来てくれました。ひづきちゃんって言ったの、私。
And so, Hizuki-chan came... wait, did I say Hizuki-chan?
あ、間違えた！AZKiちゃんが来てくれました！嬉しいね！
Oh, my mistake! AZKi-chan came to perform! I'm so happy!
というわけで、あっという間なんだけど、私口癖が「というわけで」なんだなって、今気づいちゃった。
Anyway, it's gone by in a flash. I just realized my habit is saying "Anyway".
ここからライブ後半戦です！
From here, it's the second half of the live show!
それでは5曲目、聴いてください。モニタリング。
Now, please listen to the fifth song: Monitoring.
ねえ あたし知ってるよ きみがひとり涙してるの 知ってるよ
Hey, I know. I know you're crying all alone.
びくんびくん震えてさ 声もだだ漏れなんだわ 正直に
Shaking all over, your voice is leaking out, honestly...
ちょーいえばバレてるんだし ちょーいえば聞いてんの？
to put it mildly, it's so obvious. Are you even listening?
ふつーふつー平気だよ みんな分かってないだけ
It's totally normal, everyone just doesn't get it.
もしもし ねえ大丈夫？ うん心配だから今からそっち行くね
Hello? Hey, are you okay? I'm worried so I'll go over now.
ねえ あたし知ってるよ きみがひとり涙してるの 知ってるよ
Hey, I know. I know you're crying all alone.
ぐすんぐすん凹んでさ 弱音ヒトカラでいいんじゃない？
Sobbing and depressed, complaining, isn't solo karaoke fine?
朝が来るまで一緒 ごすんもとないたって 何度だって受け止めてあげる
Together until morning, even if you cry, I'll accept you over and over.
もう我慢しないで いっぱい吐いてね ぷぅー
Don't hold back anymore, let it all out. Puu!
お願い きみが欲しいの 慰めさせて ベストフレンド
Please, i want you so bad. Let me comfort you, best friend.
愛の才能で 泣いてくれるかい
With my talent for love, will you cry?
きみのツラい 抱きしめたい ねえいいでしょう？
I want to hold you tight through your pain, hey, isn't it fine?
分け合って 乗り越えたいんだってば
I'm telling you, I want to share and overcome it.
お願い きみが欲しいの 笑い飛ばして
Please, i want you so bad. Let's laugh it off...
ホップ ステップ ジャンプ さあ行こうぜ
hop, step, jump, and let's go!
分けてくれるかい きみに重い暗い思い除きたい
Will you please share? Your heavy, dark thoughts, I want to remove them.
吸い取って救いたいんだってば
I'm telling you, I want to absorb it and save you.
見たい見たい見たい見たい見たい... のきみのおなか
I want to see, I want to see... your stomach.
見たい見たい見たい見たい見たい...
I want to see, I want to see...
ねえ あたし知ってるよ きみがひとり悔しがってるの 知ってるよ
Hey, I know. I know you're feeling frustrated all alone.
ぐすぐす終わるまで きみを消して諦めない
Until the sobbing ends, I won't erase you and give up.
ねえ あたし知ってるよ きみはできる子知ってるよ
Hey, I know. I know you're capable.
ツラい時は 弱い位でちょうどいい あたしきみの味方だよ
When times are tough, being a bit weak is just right. I'm on your side.
お願い きみが欲しいの 名前を呼んでよ
Please, i want you so bad. Call my name.
いつだって 会いに参上
And anytime I'll show up to see you.
きみはひとりか それは違う ひとりじゃない
Are you alone? That's not true, you're not alone.
もういいでしょう ソロプレイはお仕舞いなんだってば
That's enough now, i'm telling you solo-play is over.
きみがどんなときも あたし側（そば）にいるわ
No matter when you're down, I'll be by your side.
いつも見守っているわ そうよ怖くないのよ
I'll always be watching over you, yes, don't be afraid.
おおおーーー
Ohhh...
お願い きみが欲しいの 慰めさせて ベストフレンド
Please, i want you so bad. Let me comfort you, best friend.
愛の才能で 泣いてくれるかい
With my talent for love, will you cry?
きみのツラい 抱きしめたい ねえいいでしょう？
I want to hold you tight through your pain, hey, isn't it fine?
分け合って 乗り越えたいんだってば
I'm telling you, I want to share and overcome it.
お願い きみが欲しいの 笑い飛ばして
Please, i want you so bad. Let's laugh it off...
ホップ ステップ ジャンプ さあ行こうぜ
hop, step, jump, and let's go!
分けてくれるかい きみに重い暗い思い除きたい
Will you please share? Your heavy, dark thoughts, I want to remove them.
吸い取って救いたいんだってば
I'm telling you, I want to absorb it and save you.
ねえ あたし知ってるよ きみがひとり涙してるの 知ってるよ
Hey, I know. I know you're crying all alone.
ぐすんぐすん凹んでさ 弱音ヒトカラでいいんじゃない？
Sobbing and depressed, complaining, isn't solo karaoke fine?
ずっと一緒 もっと泣いたって 何度だって受け止めあげ（てあげる）
Together forever, even if you cry more, I'll accept you over and over.
もう我慢しないで出してってってってば
Don't hold back anymore, let it out, I tell you!
はーい！ということで新衣装です！
Yes! And here is my new outfit!
みんな可愛い？
Is it cute, everyone?
気になるとは思うけど、紹介は後で！
I know you're curious, but the introduction will be later!
先にゲストの方と歌うよ！
First, I'm going to sing with our guest!
どうぞ！
Here they come!
僕らよ 始まれ
Let us begin
青く 青く 果てまで
To the blue, blue end of the world
繭の底 目を覚ましたバースデイ
Awakening at the bottom of the cocoon, my birthday
ホームシックにやられそうなバス停
At a bus stop where homesickness almost takes over
何処に居たって足りない
No matter where I am, it's not enough
命は一つずつ足りない
Our lives are not enough, one by one
まだ 羽ばたくのは脳内にて 終わらないで
Fluttering wings inside my mind, don't let it end yet
まだ 不思議な夢を見る
I still dream a strange dream
二人なら
If it's the two of us...
何処までも行けると
...we can go anywhere
どうしてか 信じたくなった
For some reason, I wanted to believe it
跳ねる鼓動 誰を呼ぶの ベルの音 どうして待って
春夏秋冬 孵化は自分主導
My bounding pulse, who does the bell chime for?
Waiting through the seasons, the hatching is up to me!
あっという間に終わる祭りを前に
恐れさえも 笑い合おう
Faced with a festival that ends in the blink of an eye,
let's laugh off even our fears
共に在ろう
Let's be together
至って不完全体 故に面白くなってきた
Highly incomplete, and that's why it's getting fun!
空腹の夜を越え
Crossing the hungry nights...
空白に願い唱え
...chanting wishes into the void
諦め尽くされた世界を
Taking over a world given up on...
君とふたり占めに転げ回る
...and tumbling around with just you
混ざり合い、そして生まれ変わるような
Blending together, as if being reborn
きっと僕達だけが成せるパレード
Surely, this is a parade only we can pull off
絶対証明したい 進化したい
I absolutely want to prove it, I want to evolve
才能超えた新形態 さあ想像次第 「どうなりたい？」
A new form beyond talent, it's up to our imagination:
"What do you want to be?"
斯くも現実は不可能を敷き詰めだがり
Even though reality wants to block us with impossibilities...
過去の惜別と睨めっこしたって憂うばかり
...and staring down past partings only brings grief
今はそこに君が居る
Now, you are here by my side
未知なるバージョン
An unknown version...
覚醒前夜
...on the eve of awakening
まだ名も無きヒーロー
A still-nameless hero
行こうか
Shall we go?
僕らよ 始まれ
Let us begin
青く 青く 果てまで
To the blue, blue end of the world
至って不完全体 故に面白くなってきた<
Highly incomplete, and that's why it's getting fun!
空腹の夜を越え
Crossing the hungry nights...
空白に願い唱え
...chanting wishes into the void
諦め尽くされた世界を
Taking over a world given up on...
君とふたり占めに転げ回る
...and tumbling around with just you
混ざり合い、そして生まれ変わるような
Blending together, as if being reborn
きっと僕達こそが成せるパレード
Surely, this is a parade only we can pull off
不完全体、美しきパレード
Highly incomplete, a beautiful parade
はい！というわけで！
Alright! And with that...
ゲストの前にちょっとね、今ね
Before we continue with our guest...
東北の方で地震があったみたいですが、大丈夫でしょうか？
It seems there was an earthquake in Tohoku. Is everyone okay?
東北の方、身の回りの安全を優先でお願いします
Everyone in Tohoku, please prioritize your safety first.
気をつけるんだよ！ / 気をつけてください！
Be careful! / Please stay safe!
そして！次のゲストはリオナちゃんです！
And now, our next guest is Riona-chan!
はーい！Pla-Glowのリーダー、響咲リオナです！
ぷらぷら～よろし～！
Hello! I'm Hibiki Riona, the leader of Pla-Glow!
Pura-pura, nice to meet you!
そして、そら先輩、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Also, Sora-senpai, happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！嬉しい！
Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
今日はね、あの、最近めちゃくちゃ仲良いっていうのと
Today, well, since we've been getting really close lately...
めちゃめちゃ仲良いですしね
Yeah, we're super close!
あとお歌とダンスと言えば、
なんか今はリオナちゃんってイメージがあって
And when it comes to singing and dancing,
I've really been picturing Riona-chan lately.
一緒にあの、歌いたいと思って、呼んじゃいました！
I really wanted to sing with you, so I invited you!
本当に嬉しかったです！呼んでもらえた時！
I was so incredibly happy when you invited me!
それより、それより / はい、はい / そら先輩
By the way, by the way... / Yes? / Sora-senpai...
新衣装じゃないですか！ / そう！
You're wearing a new outfit, aren't you! / Yes!
めちゃくちゃ可愛い！ / ありがとうございます！
It's so cute! / Thank you so much!
どんな衣装なんですか？
What kind of outfit is it?
こちらはですね、去年出したアルバムの「Parallel」っていう
ジャケットで使った衣装なんですけど
This is the outfit used for the cover of "Parallel",
the album I released last year.
もう、実際にライブでも着たいと思って、仕立てて...
But I really wanted to wear it for an actual live concert,
so I had it made...
いただきました。
We received...
あら、もう、そらともさんも、そらともさんも、「ちゅー」って感じじゃないですか？
Oh, even the Soratomo, aren't they all kissing?
「ちゅー」って感じになっちゃうかもしれない。
They might end up kissing.
じゃあ、あの、シロさんを見習って
So, following Shiro-san's example...
リオナが来た意味をね、今から私も、やっていこうと思うんですけど
I think I'll show the meaning of Riona being here now...
何ですか？
What is it?
ま、みんなもね、写真がいっぱい撮りたいと思うんですね。
Well, everyone wants to take lots of photos, right?
そうですね。
That's true.
リオナ直伝のセクシーポーズ写真集
Riona's directly taught sexy pose photoshoot!
おお。
Oh.
どうですか？
How about that?
やるやる！
I'll do it, I'll do it!
スクショ大会。こんな大会？
A screenshot tournament. A tournament like this?
大会です。もう、これは。
It is a tournament, absolutely.
大会だった。
It was a tournament.
あの、セクシーなポーズを直伝、直伝？
Those sexy poses taught directly, directly?
直伝！
Directly!
伝授してくれるので
She will pass them down to me,
それをね、そらともさんに写真撮ってもらうという回でも。私は、もう画面外で。
so this is a corner where Soratomo can take photos of it. I'll stay off-camera.
え、何で何で？
Wait, why, why?
あとで一緒に撮ろうね。
Let's take them together later.
あ、オッケーです。
Ah, okay.
じゃあ、まず、
Then, first...
え、やっぱ、リオナといえば、これ、リオナといえば、もうこれですから。
Well, when you think of Riona, it's this. Riona means this.
これできるかな、私。
I wonder if I can do this.
これ、ちょっと、
This, a little...
ちょっと足をこう、私できない、ちょっと。
Put your legs like this... I can't do it, wait.
色々アウト。色々アウトなポーズ。
Various out! Various out poses.
こういうのはどうですか？こういうの。
How about something like this? This kind.
そういうのね。
Like that, right?
でも、リオナはね、いきますから。どっか。
But Riona is going. Somewhere.
あ、いいですね、いいですね。
Oh, that's nice, that's nice.
あ、いい、ちょっと右手を前に出しちゃったりして。
Ah, nice. Try putting your right hand out a bit.
あ、いい、あ、いいですね、いいですね。
Ah, nice. Oh, that's great, that's great.
あ、ちょっと、あ、いい、上手い！
Ah, wait, ah, nice! You're good!
あれ？そら先輩、セクシーの才能が
Wait? Sora-senpai, your talent for being sexy...
かなりあるんじゃないですか？
Don't you have quite a lot of it?
おお、素晴らしい！
Oh, wonderful!
え、あとはどうしようかな。
Hm, what else should we do?
ちょっと、あ、嫌だ、いいの？それ。
Wait, ah, no, is that okay? That.
そういうことじゃないの？セクシーって。
Isn't that what sexy is?
いや、ちょっと教える必要なかったですよ、これ。
No, there was really no need for me to teach you this.
あ、ちょっと、あ、ちょっと。
Ah, wait, ah, wait.
うわ、後ろからのアングルめっちゃいいな。
Whoa, the angle from behind is really good.
ちょっと。
Wait.
楽しまないでよ！
Don't enjoy it so much!
ごめんごめん。
Sorry, sorry.
あと、なんかね、こう、こういうのとかね。いや、ほら、みたいな。
And then, like, something like this. Like, "Look at this."
後ろからの、いぇーい。
From behind, yay!
あ、いいですね、いいですね。
Ah, that's nice, that's nice.
可愛い！色とりどりでめっちゃ綺麗ですね。
Cute! It's so colorful and beautiful.
そう、このグラデーションが入ってて可愛いんだよ。
Yes, this gradation is so cute.
めっちゃ可愛い！
So cute!
え、じゃあ、一緒に写ってくれますか？
Then, will you take a photo with me?
もちろん、だよ。
Of course.
いぇーい。
Yay!
そらリオポーズ考えようって言ったのに、全然考えられない。
Even though we said we should think of a Sora-Rio pose, we can't think of one at all.
なんか、クマと、なんか、リオナっぽいポーズが、
Like, a bear and, like, a Riona-like pose...
なんかリオナの公式ポーズがこれなんですけど。
Riona's official pose is actually this.
私はこうなんだよね。
Mine is like this.
そう、だから、そしたら、なんか、
Right, so then, maybe...
ほぼ似てる、みたいな。
They're almost similar.
ほぼ一緒。そしたら、クマ、クマと手、こう、
Almost the same. Then, the bear, the bear and the hand, like this...
これがいいんじゃないかって思ってるんですけど、皆さんどうですか？
I think this would be good, what does everyone think?
どうですか？
How about it?
そらリオポーズ。
Sora-Rio pose!
クマトのばし。
Bear extension!
あんきものばし。
Ankimo extension!
え、あと、あれですよ、最近私のこと飲んでるって本当ですか？
And also, is it true that you've been drinking me lately?
そう！
Yes!
リオナ茶を。
Riona tea!
貧血のリオナ茶を。
Anemic Riona tea!
すごく助かってます。
It's been a huge help.
本当ですか？
Really?
じゃあもういつでも呼び出してください。リオナ、注ぎに行くんで。
Then you can call me anytime. Riona will come to pour.
あ、ありがとうございます。そら先輩どうぞ、って。
Ah, thank you. Sora-senpai, here you go.
うわー！
Whoa!
助かる。私が助かる。
That helps. *I'm* the one being helped.
いつでもね、補給しますんで。
I'll replenish you anytime.
ありがとうございます。いつでも呼んでくださいね。
Thank you. Call me anytime.
あ、はーい！
Ah, okay!
あれ？
Huh?
吸い込まれる！吸い込まれる！吸い込まれる！
I'm being sucked in! I'm being sucked in! I'm being sucked in!
そら先輩助けて！そら先輩！
Sora-senpai, help! Sora-senpai!
あー！
Ahhh!
ほら、みんな、みんなそれをやっていくんだ。
Look, everyone, everyone is doing that!
みんなそれをやっていくんだ。
Everyone is doing that...
さあ、でもね、リオナちゃんとはね、本当に仲が良くて、いつもね、よく会うんですけど。
Well, but I'm really close friends with Riona-chan, we always meet up often.
いつもと変わらない、可愛い感じでしたね。私が消えましたね、ごめんなさい。
She was her usual cute self. I disappeared, sorry.
お水を飲みに行ってました。
I went to get some water.
はい。
Yes.
というわけで、続いてのゲストは
And so, the next guest is...
もう誰だか分かるよね？
you already know who it is, right?
この人です！
It's this person!
ときのそら お披露目誕生日 2024
[On-screen: Tokino Sora Anniversary & Birthday Party 2024]
ゲスト 風真いろは
[Guest: Kazama Iroha]
風真いろは、ただいま参上でござるー！
Kazama Iroha has arrived!
ヒビカセ / 作詞：Reol 作曲：Giga
Hibikase / Lyrics: Reol, Composition: Giga
真夜中に告げる音の警告
Sounding a warning in the middle of the night,
協和音に酔う午前零時
drunk on the chord, at 12:00 AM.
あなたが触れる光、増します熱
The light you touch increases in heat,
指先に躍らされ
made to dance by your fingertips.
感覚、即、体感
Sensation, immediately experience,
寝静まる夜、二人だけの秘密
in the quiet night, a secret just between us.
相感、即、体感
Sympathy, immediately experience,
映し出される背景に魅了されていく
becoming captivated by the projected background.
忘れないでね わたしの声を
Please don't ever forget me or my voice
画面越しでいい ちゃんと愛して
Even if it's through a screen, love me properly
ヴァーチャルだって 突き放さないで
Don't push me away just because I'm virtual
あなたの音に まだ溺れていたい固定
I still want to drown in your sound
覚えていてね わたしの声を
Please remember the sound of my voice
あなたがくれた この身すべてを
And everything of this body you gave me
見つめ合う あなたと二人
As we look at each other, just the two of us
重ねた息と 音とヒビカセ
Our breaths and sounds overlap, letting them resonate
真夜中に問う 冷え切った熱
Asking in the dead of night, the fever cooled down
待ち続けてる 午前零時
Still waiting, at the stroke of midnight
鏡写しに 飽和していく
Saturated like a mirror image
知らない音が伝う
An unfamiliar sound flows through
感覚 即 体感
Senses translate instantly into physical feeling
寝静まる夜と息遣い揃う
Matching our breathing with the quiet night
体感 即 快感
Sensation turns instantly into pleasure
錆びたロジック 今一度を焦がれる
This rusted logic longs for "just one more time"
忘れないでね わたしの声を
Please don't ever forget me or my voice
次元も越えて 飛ばすシグナル
Sending a signal that even crosses dimensions
ヴァーチャルだなんて言わないで
Don't tell me that it's only virtual
あなたの音に まだ愛されていたい
I still want to be loved by your sound
覚えていてね わたしの声を
Please remember the sound of my voice
あなたがくれた この身すべてを
And everything of this body you gave me
言の葉と 初の音が交わる
Fleeting words and a first sound intermingle
この息と 音とヒビカセ
Letting our breathing and sounds resonate
あぁ あなたの生んだ音に
Ah, I just fell in love with the sound...
ただ恋をしていたの
...of the voice that you created
悲しみ 怒り 観心 すべて
Sadness, anger, and interest... all of it
打ち鳴らす
We'll ring them out
絶えず 叫ぶ 声 連ねる
Constantly crying out, linking our voices
余熱 交ぜる 愛 絶え 艶めく
Mixing the lingering heat, love fades and glows
絶えず 叫ぶ 声 連ねる
Constantly crying out, linking our voices
余熱 交ぜる 愛 絶え 艶めく
Mixing the lingering heat, love fades and glows
魅了されていく
Increasingly fascinated
忘れないでね わたしの声を
Please don't ever forget me or my voice
画面越しでいい ちゃんと愛して
Even if it's through a screen, love me properly
ヴァーチャルだって 突き放さないで
Don't push me away just because I'm virtual
あなたの音に まだ溺れていたい
I still want to drown in your sound
覚えていてね わたしの声を
Please remember the sound of my voice
あなたがくれた この身すべてを
And everything of this body you gave me
見つめ合う あなたと二人
As we look at each other, just the two of us
重ねた息と 音とヒビカセ
Our breaths and sounds overlap, letting them resonate
あぁ...
Ah...
あなたの初の音 この声 聴かせ
Let me hear your first sound, and this voice
音 ヒビカセ
Resonate the sound
はい、というわけで、最後のゲストは、いろはちゃんでーす！
Alright, and so, our final guest is Iroha-chan!
いぇーい！ホロックスの、強い、
Yay! HoloX's strong,
イケメン、早い、かっこいい！
handsome, fast, cool!
うーん、なんかすごい、風真いろはでーす！
Mmh, somehow amazing, I'm Kazama Iroha!
いぇーい！
Yay!
おかしいな...
That's weird...
おかしいなー
そら先輩、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Sora-senpai, happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
おかしいな...
That's weird...
何がおかしいんだい？
What's so weird?
リハーサル日まではあんなにメロついてくれてたのに
Up until the rehearsal day, you were so head-over-heels for me.
すごいじゃん。今日のために整えてくれたってこと？
That's great. You mean you prepared it just for today?
今日のために、ちょっと整えさせていただきました。ありがとうございます！
Yes, I prepared myself a little just for today. Thank you so much!
コメント欄のみんなもあんなにメロついてくれてたのに、今日は全然メロついてない！
Everyone in the chat was so head-over-heels too, but today no one is!
いやいや、そんなことなかったよ！かっこいい、二人とも、って書いてあったよ！
No, no, that's not true! They wrote "both of you look so cool"!
え、本当にござるか？本当に？
Eh, really? For real?
ちょっと、もう一回見たいから「かっこいい」って書いて！
Wait, I want to see it again, so write "cool"!
「かっこいい」って、みんな「かっこいい」って書いて！
Write "cool", everyone write "cool"!
可愛い、可愛い、可愛い...可愛いのは当たり前じゃん！
Cute, cute, cute... Being cute is a given!
あ、そうだ、そうだ！
Oh, that's right!
ござるちゃんはいつでも可愛い！
Gozaru-chan is always cute!
ほら、かっこいいかっこいいって！
Look, they're writing "cool, cool"!
ありがとう！お前たちの「かっこいい」が義務だとしても、風真いろはは嬉しいぞ！
Thank you! Even if your "cool" comments are just out of obligation, Kazama Iroha is happy!
あの、1人の記念配信でも歌ってたんだけど、それすごく似合ってたから、一緒に歌いたいなと思って、呼んじゃいました！
I sang this in my solo anniversary stream too, and since it suited you so well, I wanted to sing it together, so I invited you!
嬉しい！嬉しくて、嬉しくて、死んでしまう！
I'm so happy! I'm so happy I could die!
生きて、生きて！
Live, live!
あ、生きてますよ、生きてます！
Oh, I'm alive, I'm alive!
あ、よかったよかった。
Oh, thank goodness.
いや、でもかなう...やっぱりそら先輩といえば、ボカロがめっちゃ似合うなって思ってたんで。
Well, but it came true... I've always thought Vocaloid songs really suit you, Sora-senpai.
いつかやってくんないかなって、オタクとして思ってたんですけど、まさか自分がゲストとして呼んでもらえるなんて！
As an otaku, I've always wondered if you'd do it someday, but I never expected to be invited as a guest myself!
そうだよ！
That's right!
こんなありがたいことがあっていいのか！
Is it really okay to have such a wonderful thing happen?!
でも、一緒に二人で歌ったことがなかったから、歌ってみたくて。
But we've never sung together as a duo, so I really wanted to try.
確かに！ホシアティックだとね、結構ね、
That's true! In Hoshimatic, we often...
ペアでやってることも多いんですけどね。
...end up paired up quite a lot.
フェスとかでも歌ったけど、3人とかだったから、デュエットってやったことがなくて。
We sang at festivals too, but in trios, so I've never done a duet.
確かに！ / ねー。
That's true! / Right?
ありがたいお話でございました。本当に。 / 本当に、こちらこそ。貴重な体験を...
It was a wonderful opportunity. Truly. / Same here, truly. A precious experience...
いや、こちらこそありがとうございます、本当に。
No, thank you so much, really.
はーい。 / はい。それにしても、はい、今日これ新衣装なんですよね。
Right. / Yes. By the way, this is your new outfit today, right?
そうなんですよ、新衣装なんですよ。 / 新衣装なんですよね。
That's right, it's my new outfit. / Yes, your new outfit.
どう？ / お〜。
How is it? / Ooh.
いや、ちょっと、さっきリョーナさんが結構きわどいこと言っていたんですけど、
Well, earlier Ryona-san was saying some pretty scandalous things,
やはりね、やっぱあの、ちょっとこっちのクイクイタイプオタクとして一個よろしいでしょうか？ / 何でしょう？
but as a "qui-qui" type otaku, may I ask one thing? / What is it?
やはり男というものはですね、やっぱあの一肌脱いだ姿が気になるというものでございまして。
After all, men are always curious about seeing someone show some skin.
あの、この隠されている純白が、この姿が見れるのかっていうのがすごく気になっておりまして。
So I'm really curious if we'll ever get to see the pure white hidden underneath.
だって、この下のなんかも清純感あふれるこれ、絶対みんな気になるでしょ？
I mean, this pure-looking dress underneath, everyone must be curious about it!
いや、オタクとして、もう気になりますよ、こんなの！
As an otaku, I'm just so curious about this!
そうですよね。でも、この配信の中ではちょっとまだ見せられないかな...
True. But I probably can't show it during this stream just yet...
えっ？え、もしかして、それ、それは脱げるということでしょうか？
Eh? Wait, does that mean... does that mean it can be taken off?
この配信の中では見せることはないんだけど、 / おい、どっち！
I won't be showing it during this stream, but... / Hey, which is it?!
メンバーシップに入れば...メンバーシップなら見れるかもしれない！
If you join the membership... you might see it there!
はい。いや、楽しみにしておりますので。 / こちらこそ。
Yes. Well, I'm looking forward to it. / Likewise.
メンバーシップに入れ、入れ、メンバーシップに入れ...
Join the membership, join, join the membership...
強制的！
So forceful!
クイクイ...だって、この姿が見れるんですよね。ええ。この後も楽しみにしましょうね！
Qui-qui... because we get to see this form, right? Let's look forward to it!
はい！
Yes!
というわけで、そら先輩、まだこの後も全然続くと思うんですけど、頑張ってください！
Anyway, Sora-senpai, I know there's still a lot left, but please do your best!
頑張るよ！ / プロとしてお待ちしておりますので。
I will! / I'll be waiting for you as a pro.
そうね、また後で。 / プロとして。
Right, see you later. / As a pro.
プロとして。あ、やばい、プロの世界に引き込まれてしまう。
As a pro. Oh no, I'm being drawn into the professional world.
あー！プロの世界に引き込まれ...でも、ござるわね、上品だから。
Ah! Drawn into the professional world... but I am classy, you know.
あの、お尻は撮らないで！
So, don't film my backside!
ありがとう。未来で待ってる。 / 未来で待っててくれ。
Thank you. I'll wait in the future. / Please wait for me in the future.
指なんだ！
So it's just a finger!
さあ、何、何の、何よね、あの、また後でってどういうことなんでしょうかね。
Now, what did she mean by "see you later"?
はい、プロとして。何のプロなんでしょうか。気になる方、後でライブに来てもらえると嬉しいなと思います。
Yes, "as a pro". What kind of pro? If you're curious, please come to the live show later.
さて、ちょっとお待ちくださいね。いよいよ終盤戦です。すごい。
Now, please wait a moment. Finally, it's the final stage of the show. Amazing.
お水おいしい！
Water tastes so good!
いよいよ終盤戦なんですけど、
It's finally the homestretch,
最後まで盛り上がっていってください！
but please keep the energy up until the very end!
もしかしたら、あの子が来ちゃうかもね。
Maybe that girl will show up.
聴いてください。プレイ。
Please listen. Play.
ちょけろ ちょけろ
Play dumb, play dumb
いい加減にしろ
Cut it out
どうしようもねぇ言い訳なら後で
If it's a useless excuse, later
考えてくれてやる
I'll think about it for you
王道とか下らねぇな 毎回
The royal road is so lame, every time
自意識過剰なやつ徘徊
Self-conscious ones wandering around
みんなが右往左往する間に
While everyone is running around in confusion
こちらら地に足つけてきたぜ ハイハイ
We've got our feet firmly on the ground, yes yes
どうした？みんな 浮かない顔して
What's wrong, everyone? With those gloomy faces
絵空事大歓迎よ
Pipe dreams are more than welcome
現実味ねぇよ
No sense of reality
早く楽になりたい？
Want to be at ease soon?
おねんねさしたれ nothing to do with you
Put 'em to sleep, nothing to do with you
ちょけろ ちょけろ
Play dumb, play dumb
いい加減にしろ
Cut it out
はぜろ はぜろ
Burst, burst!
責任だってとるよ墓場までは
I'll take responsibility, even to the grave
堂々とだけさせてくれよ
Just let me do it proudly
こちららマイペースなトラブルメーカー
We're self-paced troublemakers
取扱説明書隅から隅まで読んでおきな
Read the instruction manual from cover to cover
ヒヤッとしたってなぜか
Even if it gives you a chill, for some reason
ニヤッとしちゃうのおかしーな
It's funny how it makes you smirk
とめろ、とめろ、とめろ、とめろ
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it
絵空事大歓迎よ
Pipe dreams are more than welcome
現実味ねぇよ
No sense of reality
早く楽になりたい？
Want to be at ease soon?
おねんねさしたれ nothing to do with you
Put 'em to sleep, nothing to do with you
おせよ そのリセットボタン
Push it, that reset button
消せよ お前のその価値観
Erase it, your value system
どうせ何度でも元に戻せるなら
If you can reset it over and over anyway
指くわえて見てるだけじゃつまらないやいやいや
It's no fun just standing by with your finger in your mouth
ah, so i'm ready, 思いっきり
Ah, so I'm ready, with all my might
前ノリ気味止まる気ないアクセルベタ踏み
Leaning forward, no intention of stopping, pedal to the metal
ねえ are you kidding? ねえ are you kidding?
Hey, are you kidding? Hey, are you kidding?
はい、ちょ、まってここでストップ
Yes, wait, stop right here
return to the start
ぜってーやべーよ
No way, this is crazy
話がちげーぞ
This is not what we agreed on
早く楽になりたい？
Want to be at ease soon?
おねんねさしたれ
Put 'em to sleep
ラスト、いってみよう！
Let's go for the last one!
押せよ そのリセットボタン
Press it, that reset button
消せよ 前のソラの価値観
Erase it, the values of the previous Sora
本当はもう二度と 戻ってこれないから
Because actually, we can never return again
調子に乗らせて 乗らせてみるのが楽でいいのかも
Maybe letting me get carried away...
しれないな
...is easier and better.
はい！ ありがとうございました！
Alright! Thank you so much!
この曲、「トラッシュ・トラッシュ」を歌わせていただきました！
I sang the song, "Trash Trash"!
そして、この曲ではなんと、サングラスをかけたあんきもがやってきました！
And for this song, Ankimo showed up wearing sunglasses!
どうしてサングラス？
Why the sunglasses?
わあ、取れた！
Oh, they came off!
遊ぶんじゃないの、もう。
Stop playing around already!
というわけで、久々にね、あんきもと一緒に何か踊った気がするんだけど、どう？
So, I feel like it's been a while since I danced with Ankimo. How was it?
5人目のゲスト、あんきもです！
Our fifth guest, Ankimo!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ある意味、シークレットだった、めっちゃ踊るやん！
In a way, you were a secret guest. You danced so much!
ふふふ、そしてね、そんな感じで
Hehe, and well, like that...
まだね、最後にね、ちょっとお披露目もあるんだけど
We still have a little announcement at the end, but...
ここでね、まず恒例の
first, we have the usual...
お知らせがたくさんあるので
lots of announcements for you!
ここからはあんきもも一緒に告知していこうね！
So Ankimo and I will share them with you together!
聞いてください。
Please listen up.
まずは、こちら！
First up, this one!
ときのそら誕生日記念2024グッズです！
Tokino Sora Birthday Commemoration 2024 Goods!
順番に紹介していくよ！
We'll introduce them one by one!
まずは、こちら！
First is this!
Dream! そらとも法被！
Dream! Soratomo Happi!
イラストは、あるだん先生です！
The illustration is by Arudan-sensei!
テーマはライブをしている私ということで、なんとあんきももいっぱいいるんだよ。
The theme is me performing live, and there are actually lots of Ankimo too!
ね！
Right?
あの、今までもオリジナル法被自体はイベントとかで出たことはあるんですけど
We've released original happi coats at events before...
自分でオリジナルで作るのは初めてだったので
but this is the first time I've custom-made my own original one!
ぜひライブで着てきてほしいなと思って作りました！
So I made it hoping you'd wear it to my lives!
ぜひぜひみんな
Please, everyone...
楽しんでくださいね！ライブに来てください！
enjoy it and come to the live!
続いては、こちら！
Next is this!
「お部屋でのんびり」ワイドラバーマット！
"Relaxing in My Room" Wide Rubber Mat!
イェーイ！ イラストは、しわすたかし先生です！
Yay! The illustration is by Shiwatsu Takashi-sensei!
テーマは部屋でファンレターを読んでいる私で、こちらね、ホロカの
The theme is me reading fan letters in my room, and this is just the right size...
やつにね、ちょうどいいサイズになってるので
for the HoloKa cards...
ホロカを遊ぶ方、ぜひぜひ
so if you play HoloKa, please...
一緒にね、あの、持って行って遊んでもらえたら嬉しいなと思います！
bring it along and play with it! I'd be so happy!
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this!
そらとおそろいスマホリング！
Matching Smartphone Ring with Sora!
ということでね、前回販売したDJそらパーカーとデザインが一緒
This has the same design as the DJ Sora Hoodie we sold last time...
なので、それと一緒にね、合わせてスマホも私とおそろっち
so you can match your phone with me!
にしませんか？っていう感じです！
Won't you match with me?
そして、続いてはこちら！
And next is this!
そらザウルスなりきりそらちゃんぬいぐるみ！
Sorasaurs Cosplay Sora-chan Plushie!
みんな、みんながあまりにもさ、そらザウルスそらザウルスって言うからさ
Since everyone kept saying "Sorasaurs, Sorasaurs"...
でもそらザウルス自体を言うのはちょっと恥ずかしかったから
but saying "Sorasaurs" itself was a bit embarrassing...
そらちゃんぬいぐるみ、私が着ていることにするなりきりぬいぐるみにしました！
so I made a cosplay plushie where I'm wearing it!
しかもね、あのね、何そらザウルスって思う人、これ取るとフードがね
And for those wondering what Sorasaurs is, if you take off the hood...
取れると、もうピンクの衣装を着てる私みたいになるので
I look like I'm just wearing my pink outfit!
ぜひぜひフードを取り外して可愛くね、持ち歩いてくれてもいいんじゃないかなと思います！
So please feel free to take off the hood and carry it around with you!
そして、最後はこちら！
And finally, this!
ボイス！
Voices!
ASMRボイス、ボイスタイトル「届いてるよ、きみの応援」
ASMR voice, titled "I can hear your support."
ということで、部屋でファンレターを読んでいるシチュエーションになっておりますので
It's a scenario where I'm reading fan letters in my room...
ぜひぜひ皆さん、どんな風にファンレター読んでるのかなと想像しながら聞いてもらえたら嬉しいです！
so please listen to it while imagining how I read your letters!
そして、フルセット購入特典はこちら！
And here's the Full Set Purchase Bonus!
直筆サイン入り＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りポストカードと
A postcard with a handwritten signature & foil-stamped message...
特典ボイス、ボイスタイトルは「誕生日を迎えて」になります！
and a bonus voice titled "Welcoming My Birthday"!
というわけでですね、あの、皆さん急がなくて大丈夫です。
So everyone, there's no need to rush.
数量限定ではございませんので、皆さん全員分の
They are not limited in quantity, so I will sign...
サインを書かせていただきます！
for every single one of you!
いくらでも書きますので、ぜひぜひ皆さん
I'll sign as many as it takes, so please...
たくさんの人にグッズを買ってもらえたら私はとても、そらちお大喜び！
if many people get the goods, I'll be super, super happy!
なので、よろしくお願いいたします！
So please look forward to it!
以上、ときのそら誕生日記念2024グッズでした！ みんなよろしくね！
That's all for the Tokino Sora Birthday Commemoration 2024 Goods! Thank you, everyone!
続いてのお知らせは、こちら！
The next announcement is this!
大急ぎで駆け足で！ 11月ワンマンライブのときのそら生誕記念先行チケット販売開始！
In a hurry, let's be quick! Pre-sales have begun for the Tokino Sora Birthday Concert in November!
ということで、ぴあアリーナのですね、先行チケットが本日から始まっております！
The ticket pre-sales for Pia Arena MM start today!
ぴあアリーナ、え、ファンクラブに入ってる人しかできないんじゃないかって言ってた人！
For those who thought it's only open to Fan Club members...
本日から一般の皆さんも、え、販売が開始されておりますので
sales for the general public have also started today!
ぜひぜひ！もう12時から開始されております！
So please! It has already started since 12:00!
応募していただけたら嬉しいです！
I'd be so happy if you apply!
みんなでぴあアリーナでライブ楽しもう！
Let's all enjoy the live at Pia Arena!
さらに、こちら！
And furthermore, this!
その現地チケットの特典でもらえるホロカのお披露目！これもお披露目でございました！
An unveiling of the HoloKa card you get as a venue ticket bonus!
ライブの来場者特典として、限定ホロカが1枚配られます！
As an attendee bonus, you'll receive one limited HoloKa card!
全2種類のうち、1枚をランダムでお渡しするのですが、そちらの1枚を公開です！
One of the two types will be given randomly, and here is one of them!
私が描き下ろすということで、もう1個の方は
This one is illustrated by me, and the other one...
まだなので、えー
is still under wraps, so...
ね！ぜひこちらの方でちょっと
Right! Please, with this one...
満足していただけないでしょうか？
...I hope you can be satisfied with it?
そして！9周年ライブを記念して、こちら！
And! To commemorate the 9th anniversary live, this!
えー、スペシャルテレビCM放送決定！ということで
A special TV commercial broadcast is confirmed!
えー、本日の22時半から23時の間であいだで
It will air today between 22:30 and 23:00
えー、TOKYO MXさんの方の
on TOKYO MX...
ところで流れます！1度だけなので
It will air just once,
ぜひ見てくれると嬉しいなと思いますよ
so I'd be really happy if you watched it!
よろしくお願いします
Thank you so much.
そしてそして！最後のお知らせがこちら！
And next! The final announcement is this!
お待たせしました！
Sorry to keep you waiting!
こちらです！新曲「決意のソラへ」です！
Here it is! The new song, "Ketsui no Sora e"!
えー、私的には、なんかエモい感じの曲とかね、泣き曲かなって思ったんだけど
Personally, I thought it was an emotional, tear-jerking song,
でも、ディレクターさん的には、もう泣き曲とかエモとかそういうんじゃない、熱い曲！みたいな感じで
but the director said it's not just emotional or tear-jerking, but a passionate song!
オープニングにふさわしい感じのぐらいの熱い曲を作ったつもり、みたいなことを言っていたので
He said he intended to make a passionate song fit for an opening.
この後ね、MVがプレミア公開も予定されているので
After this, the MV is scheduled to have a premiere release,
各種音楽サイトでも配信もされています、ぜひたくさん
and it's also available on various music streaming sites.
聴いてもらえたら嬉しいです！
I hope you listen to it a lot!
はい、というわけでね、とっても楽しかったんですけど、いかがだったでしょうか？
Yes, so it was a lot of fun, how was it?
告知がね、あの、洪水のやってきたと思うので
Since there was a flood of announcements,
あとでみんな確認してもらえると嬉しいなと思います
I'd be happy if you could check them later.
え、そしてですね、メインは21時半から、え、アフターライブがあるんですけど
And next, the main after-live starts at 21:30,
え、スペシャルあんきもがね、なんとね、見れるかもしれないんだって。スペシャルだよ、スペシャル！
and you might get to see a special Ankimo! Yes, a special one!
えー！
Eh?!
もう、このサングラスあんきももスペシャルではあるんだけど、さらにスペシャルなあんきもが
Although this sunglasses Ankimo is already special, an even more special Ankimo
見れるかもしれない
might be seen.
そしてね、
And...
さっきも言いました、
as I said earlier,
この放送では、まあちょっとまだ
in this broadcast, well,
逃げないかな？って言ってたもの、ありますよね。いろんな撮影会しましょう！
there's something that won't run away, right? Let's do various photo sessions!
というわけで、ここまで付き合ってくれてありがとう！あんきもバイバイ！
So, thank you for sticking with me this far! Bye-bye, Ankimo!
サングラス似合ってたぞ！
The sunglasses looked good on you!
みんな吸い込まれていく
Everyone is getting sucked in...
はい、というわけでね、みなさん
All right, everyone,
いかがだったでしょうか？
how was it?
そう、こんなにね、いつもの情報の洪水が起こっていると思うのですが
I know there's been a flood of information as usual, but
ぜひぜひ、皆さんあとで観てもらえたら嬉しいです
I hope you all check it out later.
えー、最後はですね、こんだけ決意のソラへと言っておいて歌わないのはどうかなと思いますので
Lastly, since I've been talking about "Ketsui no Sora e" so much, it would be weird not to sing it,
新曲で締めたいと思います！
so I'd like to close with the new song!
それでは聴いてください、「決意のソラへ」！
Please listen to it, "Ketsui no Sora e"!
一度きりの私の物語は
My once-in-a-lifetime story
運命を超えて煌めくんだ
will transcend fate and sparkle.
行こう
Let's go!
みんな本日ありがとうございました！とっても楽しかった！
Thank you so much for today, everyone! I had so much fun!
ねえ 私より私のことを
Hey, you understand me
わかってくれるキミの存在が
even better than I understand myself...
臆病で泣き虫な心に
Your presence has cast a spell
勇気と言う魔法をかけたの
of courage on my cowardly, crybaby heart.
チクタク
Tick-tock,
時計の針だけが進む
only the hands of the clock move forward.
立ち止まってちゃダメだ
I can't just stand still.
ソラ 転び八起きがお決まりでしょう
Look, getting back up after falling is the rule, right?
一つ一つ重ねてきた
One by one, we've accumulated them,
大切なアルバムをめくるように
as if turning the pages of a precious album.
一つ一つ叶えてきた今日まで
One by one, we've fulfilled them up until today,
その全てにキミがいてくれた
and you were there for every single one.
終わりのない夢を
This endless dream...
ずっと ずっと ずっと ずっと 追いかけて行こう
Let's chase it forever and ever and ever.
行こう！
Let's go!
最高のプレゼントも外したそうだ！ありがとうございます！
I also got the best present! Thank you so much!
ねえ ここで笑い合えることが
Hey, being able to laugh together here
何よりも大事な真実
is the most important truth of all.
チクチク
Prickling,
イタズラなハートが痛む
my mischievous heart aches.
空回り 空回り 思考回路フル回転で
Going in circles, in circles, my mind is spinning at full speed.
よーいドン！
Ready, set, go!
泣いて 泣いて 泣いた夜も
Even the nights when I cried, cried, and cried
大切な人生のストーリーだから
are a precious part of my life story.
夢を 夢で 終わらせたくないんだ
I don't want to let my dream end as just a dream!
まだ見ぬ景色を 見に行こうよ
Let's go see the sights we have yet to see!
もっと もっと
More, more...
輝いて
Shine brighter...
高く 高く
Higher, higher...
飛び立とう
Let's fly away!
奇跡さえも 越えて
Even beyond miracles!
皆さんたくさんのコメント、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for all your comments, everyone!
一つ 一つ 重ねてきた
One by one, we have built them up...
未来地図のページをめくるように
...as if turning the pages of our map of the future.
泣いて 泣いて 泣いた夜も
Even the nights when I cried, cried, and cried...
大切な人生のストーリーだから
...are part of my precious life story.
夢を 夢で 終わらせたくないんだ
I don't want to let my dream end as just a dream!
まだ見ぬ景色を 見に行こうよ
Let's go see the sights we have yet to see!
終わりのない歌を
An endless song...
キミに キミに キミへと 届け
...I'll deliver it to you, to you, to you!
ずっと ずっと
Forever and ever,
誓うの 決意のソラへ
I swear, to the sky of determination...
行こう
...let's go!
本当にみんなのおかげで、最高の誕生日になりました！
Thanks to everyone, this has truly been the best birthday ever!
みんなのこと、大好きだよー！
I love you all so much!
ソロライブも来てね！
Please come to my solo live too!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
ときのそら お披露目誕生日2026
Tokino Sora Birthday Party 2026
告知あり
[Announcement Inside]